ELOI VALLÈS GUIXÀ

Adress: Avinguda Europa 4, 7e 2a, Montcada i Reixac - Barcelona Place and date of birth: Vilafranca del Penedès, 13/03/1989

Tel.: +34 610 27 57 62 Email: eloo66@gmail.com Driving license: YES



PROFILE

I am a 8 years experienced frontend developer, first with vanilla javascript and last two years with Angular. I have a solid knowledge of frontend development and I'm looking for a place to consolidate them, work with a team I can learn from and they from me, and compromise myself with the company and bring ideas to make it grow.

FORMATION

2007 - 2014 Multimedia Engineering degree

La Salle, URL, Barcelona

2015 - 2015 **Mobile Apps Development**

UOC, online

EXPERIENCE

NOVEMBER 2019 - PRESENT

KOA HEALTH. Barcelona

Health Company that provides clinical treatment for depression by completing a program through an app. Provide tools to clinicians to follow patients progress and communicate with them

Senior Frontend developer

Reporting to Tech lead

Tasks:

Develop web app with **Angular** (v. 9-13) Unit testing (jest) + UI testing (cypress) Develop mobile app with flutter

Project ownership (product refinements, onboarding new joiners...)

FEBRUARY 2019 - JULY 2019

CLARIVATE ANALYTICS. Barcelona

International research company with own product which consist in a web app which provides scientistic and legal information to companies, mainly pharmaceutic, for every country in order to sell there.

Senior Frontend Angular developer

Reporting to Tech lead

Tasks:

Develop web app with **Angular** (v. 5-7)

JANUARY 2018 - FEBRUARY 2019

CREALOGIXS. Barcelona

International company which offers digital services oriented to banking, offering both desktop and mobile development, focused on retail and corporate.

Frontend Software Engineer

Reporting to Tech lead

Tasks:

SEPTEMBER 2015 - DECEMBER 2017

NETCENTRIC. Barcelona

Young company with various offices in Europe. Web development over the Adobe platform AEM. Offers the maximum quality and performance, with a strong QA process, taking care the loading times, response times, accessibility, and more.

Frontend Software Engineer

Reporting to project manager

Tasks:

FE development of bank sites and intranet using HTML5, ECMA6, and Sass.

SEPTEMBER 2013 - AUGUST 2015

MRM-MCCANN. Barcelona

International digital publicity agency with important clients. Main clien

Junior Web Developer

Reporting to project manager

Tasks:

- Programing front end websites
- Responsive design
- Email marketing

Projects:

- Front end design Caprabo's website
- Landings for Maggi and Unilever
- Email campaigns for Nestle, Caprabo, Ikea..

Achievements:

- Programing the front end of full website
- Responsive designs with Boostrap

PREVIOUS EXPERIENCE

2 years in a startup developing smartTV app (Javascript) as trainee

LANGUAGES

Spanish: Native Catalan: Native English: Fluid

First Certificate in English. Sherwood Academy.

COMPUTER SKILLS AND TECHNICAL KNOWLEDGE

+++++ Angular (2+), Typescript, HTML5, JavaScript6, CSS, Sass

++++ Ionic, jest, cypress

+++ Nodejs, Flutter

Management and communications tools

Git, Jira, Confluence, Slack

Agile working methodologies